So I'm looking at the responses to my last video.
I'm wondering why I do not see more of my peers
speaking to the things that are happening to affect our world.
With our exposure, we're not here to just play roles on screen.
We have a role to play in using our platforms for change.
And I guess maybe people are internalizing this message
as it relates to what they can or can't do.
But I'm talking about public-facing people with lots of dollars.
And I'm just wondering, at what point do we realize
how absolutely inane it sounds to consistently say,
with no problem,
well, yeah, I mean, they can't speak up
because then they're gonna, you know,
what if they don't get booked for films?
Or like, what about they lose their audience?
Like, what?
When does that stop being a valid or valuable reason
for allowing it to go on around us
and keep posting memes?
So I thought I was saying something.
And I realize that for a lot of y'all,
you're completely fine.
You are completely fine with your public-facing figures
being completely apolitical,
saying nothing,
and just being on screen.
So fuck do I know.